[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[BILLY] I'm sorry, I did
not quite catch your name.
[DISTORTED SCREAMING]
[MAX] What happened?
Help me.
[SCREAMING] No!
[THUNDERCLAP]
Which one?
I don't know.
Hey, there's nothing to
worry about anymore, okay?
It doesn't make sense.
What doesn't make sense?
Heather.
The blood.
The ice.
Heather had a fever,
so she took a cold bath,
but she's better now.
That has to be it.
I don't know where that
blood came from, but...
we saw her.
We both saw her. She's totally fine.
What about Billy?
What about him?
He seemed wrong.
[CHUCKLES] Wrong is
kind of like his default.
But it's nice to know
he's not a murderer,
because that would've totally sucked.
[CHUCKLES]
Who... is that?
See, this is why you can't just
hang out with Mike all the time.
This is Wonder Woman.
AKA Princess Diana.
She's from Paradise Island,
which is, like, this hidden island
where there are only
women Amazon warriors.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[MRS. DRISCOLL SCREAMING]
Let me go! Let me go!
Doris, we need you to
stay calm for us, okay?
- Stay calm.
- I have to go back!
I have to go back!
Okay, so,
you two want to explain to
me what in the name of Jesus
just happened here?
[AMBULANCE DOORS CLOSING]
[SIREN WAILING]
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[SHRIEKING]
[PANTING]
[STRAINING]
[MUFFLED] Tom!
[SOBBING]
[TOM SOBS]
- [ECHOING FOOTSTEPS]
- [GASPS]
[TOM WHIMPERS]
Hi, Daddy.
Heather...
sweetie...
whatever this is,
whatever he's got you into,
you don't have to do this.
You can stop this.
There is no stopping it, Daddy.
[GASPS]
You'll see.
[JANET SOBBING]
No.
[WHIMPERING]
[SOBBING]
Heather, please! Heather!
Try not to move.
No.
- [GASPS]
- [GRUNTS]
Heather!
[CREATURE SNARLING]
[ROARING]
Jesus Christ.
[HEAVY FOOTSTEPS]
[SNARLING AND ROARING]
[TOM WAILS]
[TOM] No.
[SNARLING]
[TOM] No...
[SCREAMING]
[MUFFLED GRUNTS]
[CREATURE SNARLING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[BIRDSONG]
[GROANS]
[COUGHS]
[JOYCE] Hey, careful.
- [VOICE ECHOING] Careful.
- [HOPPER COUGHS]
Here.
Hey.
Joyce.
[HOPPER SIGHS]
[RETCHING]
Oh.
Here, here, here.
[COUGHING, VOMITING]
It's okay.
[LOUD VOMITING]
That's it. Got it?
[GROANS]
- Here.
- How long have I been out?
A while.
You've been drifting in and out.
Yeah, but how did I get here?
Slowly.
- What's the last thing you remember?
- Some thug attacked me.
- Hey, you need to rest.
- No, I'm fine.
- No, you're not fine, Hop...
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
[EXCLAIMS]
Um...
- Where are my clothes?
- Uh...
Uh...
[SHARP EXHALE]
They were soaked.
I mean, did you recognize him?
- Who?
- The thug.
[HOPPER] Well, I didn't get a good look.
Well, I mean, he's gotta
be government, right?
Yeah, but if he's government,
what's he doing slinking around?
W-Why is he running?
You know, why didn't we
find anything down there?
Let's ask him.
What is that?
His license plate.
- What are the dashes?
- Well, they're blanks.
There was... I think it
was either an H or a P
with the part rubbed off.
And there was definitely a Y.
For sure.
And that, I think, was a B,
but it could've been an eight.
And that... Wait...
I think you should stick to sales.
Can't you run a search or something?
I just think you have to
lower your expectations.
I mean, this is a
state government agency.
Gonna take weeks before
they find a match.
- Weeks?
- If we're lucky.
And, I mean,
what are the odds that this guy
registers a car in his own name?
It wasn't a car.
[CLEARS THROAT] Uh,
what are you wearing?
What do you mean it wasn't a car?
[LUCAS OVER RADIO] Do you copy?
This is a code red.
[RADIO STATIC POPS]
I repeat, this is a code red.
Max. Do you copy?
- This is a code red.
- [MAX SCOFFS]
Shut...
up.
She turned it off.
[PHONE RINGING]
[SCOFFS] You've got to be kidding me.
I'm sleeping. Go away.
[MIKE] This is Mike. Do not hang up.
Something happened, something bad.
Our very lives can be at stake.
- What are you talking about?
- Just come over to my house.
We'll explain everything.
- [MAX] What?
- Hurry.
[CLICK, DIAL TONE DRONES]
What did he say?
Try Dustin again.
He's not answering.
So, try him again.
Dustin, do you copy?
I repeat, this is a code red.
[DUSTIN] That keycard opens
the door, but unfortunately,
the Russian with this keycard
also has a massive gun.
Whatever's in this room,
whatever's in those boxes,
they really don't want
anybody finding it.
But there's gotta be a way in.
Well, you know...
I could just take him out.
- Take who out?
- The Russian guard.
What? I sneak up behind him,
I knock him out, and I
take his keycard. It's easy.
Did you not hear the part
about the massive gun?
Yes, Dustin, I did.
And that's why I would be sneaking.
Ah.
Well, please, tell me
this, and be honest,
have you ever actually... won a fight?
Okay, that was one time...
Twice. Jonathan. Year prior?
Listen, that doesn't count.
Why wouldn't it? Because it looks
like he beat the shit out of you.
- It was...
- You got a fat lip, crooked nose,
- swollen eye, a lot of blood...
- ... things that all added up...
That just might work.
[STEVE] Robin.
Hey, Robin! Hey, what...
what are you doing?
- I need cash.
- Well, half of that's mine.
- Where're you going?
- To find a way into that room,
a safe way.
And, in the meantime, sling ice cream,
behave, and don't get beat up.
I'll be back in a jiff.
Oh, dude.
Come on, man, not my scooper.
[PHONE RINGING]
[DRAWER OPENS, CLOSES]
[MAN] If he gets us the
layout by noon, we can.
[WOMAN] Okay, I'll let him know.
[MAKES CHOKING NOISE]
[LAUGHS]
Dunno if they'll go through with it,
but I just thought you should know.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Nancy.
Jonathan.
[TOM] I've worked at this
paper for twenty-five years.
Twenty-five...
years.
Now, we're a small-town paper,
but we have something
the big papers don't have:
trust.
- The trust of our community.
- Tom, if you just...
Do you know how I built that trust?
By placing my faith in something
the two of you don't
seem to value a whole lot:
facts.
Facts.
So, while we're here,
let's go over the facts.
Fact one: you disobeyed a direct
order to stop pursuing this story.
Two: you falsely identified
yourselves as reporters,
repeatedly lying to an elderly woman.
Three: you broke into her
home, committing trespass.
Four: she almost died
en route to the hospital.
She would've died if we hadn't shown up!
Whatever disease that rat
had clearly passed to her...
Five! Mrs. Driscoll is
a paranoid schizophrenic.
You didn't know that, did you?
Now...
disease-carrying rats?
The second coming of the plague?
Does this sound credible to you,
or perhaps does this sound more like
the delusions of a very sick old lady?
- I didn't know that.
- Her family's furious.
So furious, in fact, they've
threatened litigation.
- Litigation?
- That's crazy.
For once, we agree.
This is crazy.
In fact, in my entire
professional career,
I've never dealt with
anything quite like it.
But hopefully,
hopefully, you've learned
something valuable here.
You've learned...
how in the workplace,
in the real world,
there are consequences to your actions.
Which brings me to my sixth and final...
fact.
You're fired.
Both of you.
[WILL] I didn't think
it was anything at first.
I mean, I think I just
didn't want to believe it.
The first time I felt it
was at Day of the Dead.
[FLUTTERING SOUND]
- Power went out that night, too.
- And then I felt it again
at the field near the
Nelson farm the next day.
[GASPS]
Then again yesterday
outside Castle Byers.
[FLUTTERING SOUND]
[LUCAS] Will!
What does it feel like?
It's almost like...
You know when you drop
on a roller coaster?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
- No.
- It's like...
everything inside your body
is just sinking all at once, but...
this is worse.
Your body...
it goes cold and...
and you can't breathe.
I've felt it before,
whenever he was close.
- [THUNDERCLAP]
- [SNARLING]
Whenever who was close?
The Mind Flayer.
Go away!
I closed the gate.
I know, but...
what if he never left?
What if we locked him out here with us?
This is him.
All of him.
But, that day on the field,
a part of him attached itself to me.
[HYPERVENTILATING]
My mom got it out of me...
Get the hell out of my son!
... and Eleven closed the gate.
[SCREAMING]
But the part that was still in me,
what if it's still in our world?
In Hawkins.
I don't understand. The Demodogs
died when El closed the gate.
[MAX] If the brain dies, the body dies.
We can't take any chances.
We need to assume the worst.
The Mind Flayer's back.
[WILL] Yeah. And if he is,
he'd want to attach
himself to someone again.
A new me.
A new host.
How can you tell if someone is a host?
[HOPPER GRUMBLES]
Hey, is he in?
- Yes, he's busy at the moment, but...
- Great.
Excuse me.
You should sit down.
... wouldn't listen...
Uh...
Tony, hold on.
Let me, uh...
I might have to... Let
me call you back. Okay.
Thanks.
- Jim.
- I know, I know.
You're busy. I'm gonna
make this fast, I promise.
Is there...
some kind of problem?
Yeah. You might say that.
Um, I'm looking for the name of a guy.
The name of a guy.
Yeah, I think you might know this guy.
- Okay.
- He was here the other day.
Rides a motorcycle.
Big build, square jaw, dark hair.
He's probably military,
maybe ex-military?
Is this ringing... any bells?
Uh... [CHUCKLES]
I don't think so.
Really?
'Cause it was just two days ago.
This was right before I saw you.
Oh!
- You know what?
- What?
Could be the maintenance guy.
- Maintenance.
- Yeah. I can't remember his name.
Oh, God... Uh...
Gary or John or something.
Candice will have his name on file.
We've had trouble with the
plumbing. Clogged toilets and...
sinks with minds of
their own. [CHUCKLES]
You meeting with a
lot of plumbers, Larry?
Excuse me?
This guy, when I saw him, he
was coming out of your office.
Okay, well, I don't remember that.
I shake a lot of hands, you know?
Do you remember when I caught
you passed out in the hideaway
with all that powder all over your nose?
- You remember?
- Jim, come on, now.
Do you remember when my boys
found you and Candice going at it
like a couple of bunnies in
the back of your Cadillac?
Do you remember that?
Does your wife remember that?
You, uh... [CLEARS THROAT]
You really wanna play this game?
Huh?
Not a game, Lar.
Okay.
Those pills you used
to swallow like candy.
I can't recall, did you have
a prescription for those?
Or how about drinking on duty?
[CHUCKLING]
Yeah.
We have some real fun
stories about that.
[CHUCKLES]
One call to Tom at the Post...
and you're done, buddy.
You're gone.
Oh, and, please,
don't give me that
dead daughter sob story,
'cause I just don't care.
Now, if you don't mind,
I really am rather busy.
Operating directors...
[LARRY GRUNTS] Damn it!
[WAILING]
My nose! You broke my goddamn nose!
And your friend almost
killed me last night,
so I'd say we're still not even.
Larry?
- [HOPPER] Let's cut the crap, Larry!
- Larry!
- Who is this guy? Government? Military?
- You're making a big mistake.
Who is he?
It's Arnold Schwarzenegger.
- [CANDICE] Larry!
- [LARRY GROANS]
Who you calling? The police?
That is a nice ring
you got there, Larry.
Are you insane?
I don't know.
Let's find out.
[GRUNTS] Okay, okay,
okay. Be cool, be cool.
I don't know his name, I swear.
- [SIGHS]
- [SCREAMS] Ah, ah, ah!
But you know him.
He... He gives me things sometimes.
What kind of things?
Money. Presents. Aah! Gifts.
Who is this guy, Santa Claus?
Starcourt. Starcourt.
He works for Starcourt.
- The mall?
- Yes, yes.
Yeah, right.
Aah! I swear! I swear!
I swear! Starcourt.
They... They own the mall.
They want to expand to East Hawkins.
They needed property, some land.
Some people didn't want to sell,
so I leaned on them
a little. That's all.
I swear, that's all.
[SIGHS, GROANS]
[GROANS]
- Why do they want this land?
- I don't know!
You have records of these
purchases, these, uh...
these land purchases?
[BREATHING RAPIDLY]
You don't want to mess
with these people, Jim.
I think you should worry
about yourself right now,
Larry, not about me.
The records.
Where are they?
- [LARRY GROANS]
- Larry?
[HOPPER] He just bumped his head.
- Just a little boo-boo, right, Lar?
- [GRUNTS]
Have a nice day.
Larry!
[NANCY] It's bullshit.
So, according to Tom,
Driscoll's just a schizophrenic?
And that rat is just a rat?
And it's all, what,
some big coincidence?
You know what I think?
I think Tom was on drugs.
- What?
- Did you see him?
He was sweating like crazy.
And his palms were clammy.
- He looked awful.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Oh, is this funny to you?
- No.
No, it's just kind of incredible.
Incredible?
Yeah, incredible how you just
continue to convince yourself.
What's that supposed to mean?
I told you over and
over to drop this story.
- That it was a bad idea.
- [SCOFFS]
But you refused, and now, I'm screwed.
It's a summer job. Your
life is hardly over.
I don't live in a two-story
house on Maple Street.
My dad doesn't earn six figures.
Hell, he isn't even around.
God, here comes the
Oliver Twist routine.
Mortgage, college tuition.
You know, they're real things, Nancy.
Things that you don't care about,
only because you don't have to.
- I didn't realize I lived in a bubble!
- Well, you do!
You want everything handed
to you on a silver platter.
I mean, we were interns, Nancy!
Interns!
What did you expect, that you
would make star reporter in a month?
Crack the big case?
You sound just like them.
You realize that, right?
Just like Bruce and those assholes...
Yeah, yeah, those assholes gave us jobs.
Is that what that was?
That was humiliating.
Humiliating.
Yeah, the real world sucks.
Deal with it like the rest of us.
You don't know what it's like.
Neither do you.
[SCOFFS]
Well, then, I guess we just don't
understand each other anymore.
Yeah, I guess not.
Hey, you're home early.
Yeah. Light day.
[NANCY SNIFFLES]
[ROBIN] It is fascinating
what 20 bucks will get you
at the County Recorder's Office.
Starcourt Mall.
The complete blueprints.
Not bad.
So, this is us, Scoops,
and this is where we want to get.
I mean, I don't really see a way in.
There's not,
if you're talking
exclusively about doors.
Air ducts.
Exactly.
Turns out, this secret room
needs air just like any old room.
And these air ducts
lead all the way...
here.
Flashlight.
Thank you.
Yeah, I don't know, man. I don't know
if you can fit in here. It's, like...
super tight.
I'll fit.
Trust me. No collar bones, remember?
Uh, excuse me?
Oh, he's, uh... Yeah,
he's got some disease.
Chry, uh... It's chrydo, um...
Something. Yeah, I dunno.
He's missing bones and stuff.
He can bend like Gumbo.
You mean Gumby.
I'm pretty sure it's Gumbo.
- Steve, just shut up and push me!
- Okay.
I'll push ya.
- Not my feet, dumbass. Push my ass.
- [STEVE] What?
Touch my butt! I don't care!
- Come on! Harder! Push harder!
- I'm pushing!
You're playing with my legs.
I'm not playing,
I have terrible footing.
- Come on!
- I'm gonna just shove you, ready?
- [DUSTIN] Just shove me?
- One, two...
- Shit.
- [STEVE] That work?
- [DUSTIN] One more time.
- Ahoy, sailors! All hands on deck!
Ahoy!
- [BELL DINGING]
- [ERICA] Come on.
Get over here and serve me some samples.
I don't know. He looks
pretty normal to me.
Normal? How many times have
you seen him with a shirt on?
I mean, it's a little weird.
More than a little.
He was in a tub with ice.
The Mind Flayer likes it cold.
- Plus everything else...
- But he's lounging at the pool,
which is, like, the least
Mind Flayer thing ever.
Not necessarily.
The Mind Flayer likes to hide.
He only used me when he needed me.
It's like... like you're dormant.
And then, when he needs you,
you're activated.
Okay, so we just...
wait until he gets activated.
No. What if he hurts someone?
Or kills someone.
We can't take that chance.
We need to find out if he's the host.
- Where are you going?
- I have an idea. Boys only.
- Seriously?
- Just trust me on this one.
Okay, so we wait until the pool
closes, until everyone leaves,
and we somehow get him
to come from here and...
get him into here.
- Hey, shut the door!
- [MAN] Hey, come on, kid, shut it!
I think I just threw up in my mouth.
And look, the controls are
right here. It's perfect.
- Will it get hot enough?
- 220 degrees.
We just have to figure
out how to get him in here.
- Then we lock him in...
- Heat him up...
No matter what happens, we'll know.
We'll know for sure.
Hmm...
- Yeah, I don't know.
- You don't know if you can fit?
Oh, I can fit. I just
don't know if I want to.
Are you claustrophobic?
[SNICKERS] I don't have phobias.
- Okay, well, what's the problem?
- The problem is,
I still haven't heard what's in this
for Erica.
[NAUTICAL TUNE PLAYING]
More fudge, please.
Go on.
[ROBIN] All right.
You see this? This is the
route you're gonna take.
Then we just wait till the
last delivery goes out tonight.
Then you knock out the grate,
jump down, open the door.
- Then you find out what's in those boxes?
- Exactly.
[ERICA] Mm-hmm.
And you say this guard is armed.
Yes, but he won't be there.
- And booby traps?
- Booby traps?
- Lasers, spikes in the wall?
- What?
You know what this half-baked
plan of yours sounds like to me?
Child endangerment.
We'll be in radio contact
with you the whole time...
Ah, ah, ah!
Child endangerment.
Erica? Hi. Uh...
We think these Russians want
to do harm to our country.
Great harm. Don't you love your country?
You can't spell
"America" without "Erica".
[SLURPING LOUDLY]
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Oddly, that's, uh, totally true.
So, so, don't do this for us.
Do it for your country.
Do it for your fellow man.
- [SLURPING CONTINUES]
- Do this for America... Erica.
Ooh!
I just got the chills.
Oh, yeah, from this float,
not your speech.
Know what I love most
about this country?
Capitalism.
- Do you know what capitalism is?
- Yeah.
- It means this is a free market system.
Which means people get
paid for their services,
depending on how valuable
their contributions are.
And it seems to me,
my ability to fit into that little vent
is very, very valuable to you all.
So, you want my help?
This USS Butterscotch
better be the first of many.
And I'm talking free ice cream
for life.
[HOPPER WHISTLES]
Wow, I love the place, Lar.
Hey, you shoot that fella yourself?
[LARRY WINCES] That's...
That's not real.
No shit!
All right, so...
what exactly are we looking at?
Land deeds, transfers of property.
So your buddies at Starcourt,
they suddenly start buying
up all this property.
- They tell you why?
- I already told you,
they don't tell me anything.
They're just using you, I get it.
What I don't get
is why you have a bunch of land deeds
in a safe in your bedroom.
These people, Jim,
they're bad news.
So, what, this is blackmail?
- Protection.
Hold on a second.
Hey, what is it?
Hess Farm, Henry's place,
Bullocks...
Look, they're all here.
They're all in Southeast
Hawkins, right near Jordan Lake.
And what else is near Jordan Lake?
The power plant.
Four nights ago, there
was a huge power outage,
- and the next day...
- Your magnets fell.
Yeah, I mean, Scott
says that this machine
would take a massive
amount of power to run.
- Yeah.
- So, what if this machine
that we've been talking
about really does exist,
and the reason that we
didn't find it at the lab
is because it isn't at the lab,
it's at one of these properties.
Um...
I want you to... forget about sales.
I want you to come work
for me at the Hawkins PD.
And have to look at your face
every day? I don't think so.
[CLATTERING]
Larry!
Hey!
Hey, where do you
think you're going, pal?
[LARRY SCREAMS]
- [KNOCKING]
- [KAREN] Nancy?
Nance?
[SNIFFLES]
[NANCY] Maybe Jonathan's right.
To be honest, I wasn't
thinking about him.
I wasn't thinking about anyone, really.
I just...
I wanted to be right.
- I wanted to be right so badly.
- And were you?
I thought so.
But maybe I just...
don't want to admit that I'm wrong,
because if I'm wrong, then...
You're what everyone thinks you are.
Just a kid who has no
idea what she's doing.
[SIGHS]
It's not easy out there, Nance.
I know.
People are always saying you can't.
That you shouldn't.
That you're not...
smart enough, not good enough.
[SIGHS]
This world, it...
it beats you up again and
again until eventually, I...
Most people, they just...
they just stop trying.
But you're not like that.
You're a fighter.
You always have been.
I honestly don't know where
you get it from. [CHUCKLES]
Dad.
[BOTH LAUGH]
I think you were swapped in the
hospital, to tell you the truth.
No.
I get it from you, Mom.
I get it from you.
Well, wherever you get it from,
I'm proud of you.
Proud of me for getting fired?
That you stood up for yourself.
That you stood up to those...
shitheads.
Mom!
Yes, those shitheads.
[CHUCKLES, SNIFFLES]
And if you believe in this story...
Look at me, Nancy.
... finish it.
Then go sell it to The Indianapolis
Star or whatever and...
I mean, can you imagine their faces
when they read a story
about their own town
in a big paper like that?
That would be...
pretty amazing.
So, why not?
Why not?
Finish it.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[LIGHTER CLICKS]
Uh, Will?
Um, you know, about yesterday...
It's fine, Lucas.
You don't have to say anything.
I know, but it's just...
It was a really cool campaign.
- And Mike and I, we should've never...
- I don't care anymore, Lucas.
I really don't.
We have bigger things
to worry about now.
This should hold him.
[MIKE SIGHS]
Hey, I found the breakers.
Whoa, that thing is super creepy.
Let me see it.
I think this'll work. Right, buddy?
[IN SQUEAKY VOICE] Right, Mike.
[MIKE CHUCKLES]
Hey, El...
I just wanted to say...
You know when I said Nana was sick?
She wasn't. I lied.
- I know.
- Right, right, right. No, I just...
think it was important for
you to know the context.
Hopper, he went all crazy on me,
telling me I'm spending
way too much time with you.
He made me lie. I mean,
you're the most important
thing to me in the world.
What if he's right?
- What?
- Hop.
No, no, no, no.
He's just some angry
old man who hates joy.
But if I only see you,
and I'm a different species than you,
then I should be with my species more.
What are you talking about?
[GASPS]
Did you spy on me?
- That's totally against the rules.
- I make my own rules.
- [MAX] Mike, are you there?
- Yeah!
- Where are you guys?
- I'm coming. Just...
hold on a second.
Shit!
[MAX] God, I hope it's not you.
I really hope it's not you.
[LIGHTER CLICKING]
[RADIO STATIC POPS]
[ROBIN] Erica, do you copy?
[ERICA] Mm-hmm. I copy.
- You nerds in position or what?
- [ROBIN] Yeah, we're in position.
It's all quiet here, so
you've got the green light.
Green light, roger that.
Commence Operation Child Endangerment.
Can we maybe not call it that?
See you on the other side.
Nerds.
[GRUNTS]
[STRAINING]
[LARRY] Winnie!
Winnie, is that you?
- Larry?
- Winnie, upstairs in the bedroom!
Baby.
Oh, my God, baby, what happened?
Get me a phone.
- Baby...
- Get me a goddamn phone!
[JOYCE] Anything?
[HOPPER] No.
This place is dead.
All right, where to next?
[JOYCE] Hess Farm.
[ERICA COUGHS, GRUNTS]
All right, nerds.
I'm there.
Do you... Do you see anything?
Yeah, I see those boring
boxes you're so excited about.
- [ROBIN] Any guards?
- Negative.
- Booby traps?
- If I could see them,
they'd be pretty shit traps,
- wouldn't they?
- Thank you for that.
[YELLS]
I'm in.
Oh, God.
[KLAXON WAILS]
Free ice cream
for life.
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[SHOWER RUNNING]
[BILLY GRUNTING]
[SIGHS]
[SHOWER STOPS]
[CLANGING]
Pool's closed.
[METALLIC SCRAPING, CLANGING]
Hey.
Do you hear me?
Pool is closed!
[MIKE] Billy!
Who's there?
[MIKE, IN SING-SONGY VOICE] Billy!
[IN SING-SONGY VOICE] Who's there?
[ECHOING LAUGHTER]
[MIKE] Billy!
You think this is funny, huh?
[MIKE'S LAUGHTER ECHOES]
[MIKE] Billy.
Come and find me.
I find you, it is your funeral.
[MIKE] Come and get me. Come on!
[MIKE'S VOICE ECHOES]
[MIKE] Billy!
[MIKE LAUGHS]
Got you.
[BILLY CACKLES]
[MIKE] Come and get
me, you piece of shit.
[GRUNTING]
[MIKE, ON RADIO] Hey.
Behind you.
Hi.
- [ELEVEN GRUNTS]
- [BILLY GROANS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [MIKE] Now!
[CHAIN RATTLING]
[YELLS]
[BILLY GRUNTS]
- Come on.
- Got it.
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING, PANTING]
Max.
[BILLY'S VOICE ECHOES]
Do it.
[DISTANT SIREN WAILING]
[INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT ON PA]
Hi.
[GRUNTS]
Uh, I'm here to see Doris Driscoll.
I think she was admitted last night.
Name and relation?
Uh... Nancy...
Driscoll.
I'm...
Nancy Driscoll.
Her... granddaughter.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[STEADY BEEPING]
- [SNIFFING]
- [HEART MONITOR BEEPING]
[SNIFFING]
[AIR HISSING]
That's definitely not Chinese food.
Uh, maybe you guys should,
you know, stand back.
- No.
- Just...
- Just step back, okay?
- No.
- Step back. Seriously.
- No! No!
If you die, I die.
Okay.
[AIR HISSING]
What the hell?
What is that?
[RUMBLING]
Was that just me, or did the room move?
[WHISPERING] Booby traps.
[MECHANICAL WHIRRING]
You know what? Let's
just grab that and go.
[AIR HISSING]
Which one do I press, Erica?
Just press the damn button, nerd.
Which one? I'm pressing
the button, okay?
- Press "open door".
- I'm pressing "open door".
Just open the... Press the other button.
[ROBIN] Out of the way so
she can push the button...
- Would you stop?
- I'm trying.
Would you let me just
do it? Would you stop?
- [ROBIN] Just open the door!
- [CLANG]
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[SCREAMING]
Oh, shit.
[BEEPING RAPIDLY]
[MRS. DRISCOLL BREATHING RAPIDLY]
[BREATHING RAPIDLY AND COUGHING]
[BEEPING INTENSIFIES]
Max! Let me out of here!
[BILLY'S VOICE ECHOES]
Let me out.
[BILLY] You kids...
You think this is funny?
You kids think this is some
kind of sick prank, huh?
You little shits think this is funny?
What is this?
Open the door.
Open the door!
Open the goddamn door!
[BILLY SCREAMS]
We're at 220.
[BILLY GRUNTS]
[BILLY SOBBING]
[BILLY] It's not my fault.
It's not my fault.
It's not my fault, Max.
I promise you, it's not my fault.
What's not your fault, Billy?
I've done things, Max. Really...
bad things.
I didn't mean to.
He made me do it.
Who made you do it?
I don't know, it's like a shadow.
[BILLY] Like a giant shadow.
Please, Max.
What did he make you do?
It's not my fault, okay? Max, please.
Please, believe me,
Max, it's not my fault.
I tried to stop him, okay? I did.
[BILLY SNIFFLES]
Please believe me, Max.
Please believe me.
Billy, it's gonna be okay.
Max, please.
[MAX] It's gonna be okay.
We want to help you.
You just have to talk to us, okay?
You have to talk to us.
- [MAX] I believe you, Billy.
- [FLUTTERING SOUND]
We'll figure it out together, okay?
[SHUDDERS] I feel him.
- He's activated.
- [MAX] I need you to trust me. Please.
- Max, get away from the door.
- What?
- Get away from the door!
- [YELPS]
- [YELLS]
- [GASPS]
Let me out, you bitch! Let me out!
I'll fucking gut you!
[BILLY GRUNTS]
[ROARS] Let me out!
[GROANS]
Max, come on!
[GURGLES]
[SQUELCHING]
[GRUNTING]
[BILLY GRUNTS]
[SQUELCHING]
[ROARING]
[SCREAMING]
[RAPID BEEPING]
- [MRS. DRISCOLL WAILING]
- Oh, my God.
[BILLY ROARING]
[RAPID BEEPING]
[WAILING]
[ROARING]
- He can't get out, can he?
- No way.
- [POUNDING ON DOOR]
[ROARING]
[GRUNTING]
[ALL GASP]
[BILLY BREATHES HEAVILY]
[ELEVEN SCREAMS]
[BILLY GROANS]
- [GASPING]
- [GRUNTING]
[CRACKING NOISE]
[ELEVEN YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
- [CRACKING NOISE]
- [BILLY GROANS]
[ROARING]
[MONSTROUS WAILING]
[SCREAMING]
- [CLANGING]
- [BILLY ROARS]
[ELEVEN GASPS, SCREAMS]
[CHOKING]
[CHOKING, GASPING FOR AIR]
[COUGHING]
[ELEVEN] No!
No! No!
[ELEVEN SCREAMS] No!
[CHOKING] No...
[GASPING FOR AIR]
- [MIKE YELLS]
- [BILLY GROANS]
Go to hell, you piece of shit!
- [PANTING]
- [CLANGING]
[GROANS]
[SCREAMS]
[YELLING]
[SCREAMING, GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING]
[ELEVEN PANTING]
[BILLY WAILS]
[BOTH SCREAMING]
[INAUDIBLE]
[SQUELCHING]
[BILLY WAILS]
["WE'LL MEET AGAIN" PLAYING]
♪ We'll meet again... ♪
- [HEATHER] The girl, was it her?
- [BILLY] Yeah.
It was her.
She knows now. She knows about me.
She could've killed me.
Yes.
But not us.
- Not us.
- ♪ We'll meet again ♪
♪ Don't know where ♪
♪ Don't know when ♪
♪ But I know we'll meet again ♪
♪ Some sunny day ♪
[LOW RUMBLING]
♪ Keep smiling through... ♪
[LOW GROWLING]
[ROARING]
♪ ... drive the dark clouds far away ♪
♪ So will you please say hello ♪
♪ To the folks that I know ♪
♪ Tell them I won't be long ♪
♪ They'll be happy to know ♪
♪ That as you saw me go ♪
♪ I was singing this song ♪
♪ Keep smiling through ♪
♪ Just like you ♪
♪ Always do ♪
♪ Till the blue skies
drive the dark clouds ♪
♪ Far away ♪
♪ So will you please say hello ♪
♪ To the folks that I know ♪
♪ Tell them I won't be long ♪
♪ They'll be happy to know ♪
♪ That as you saw me go ♪
♪ I was singing this song ♪
♪ We'll meet again ♪
♪ Don't know where ♪
♪ Don't know when ♪
♪ But I know we'll meet again ♪
♪ Some sunny day ♪
[MONKEY SCREECHING]