[distorted cheering]
[yelling and cheering]
["R.O.C.K. in the U.S.A." playing]
♪ Rockin' in the U.S.A. ♪
[squealing and laughing]
♪ Hey! R.O.C.K. in the U.S.A... ♪
- [man] One for each of you.
- Thanks.
[vendor] Have fun.
♪ R.O.C.K. in the U.S.A. ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Rockin' in the U.S.A. ♪
- [man 2] There you go.
- Yeah!
["The Washington Post March" playing]
[crowd cheering]
- [band stops]
- Now, doesn't that just lift your spirits?
[cheering]
Let's give another big hand
for the Hawkins High Marching Band!
[cheering]
I hope you're all having
a good time tonight.
- [crowd cheers]
- Are you having a good time?
[cheering]
[Larry] I can't hear you!
Are you having a good time?
[loud cheering]
[chuckles] I want you to know
that we spared no expense
to provide you with the very best
entertainment that money can buy!
[fair worker] Keep your arms inside.
Uh-oh! Dad can't get out now.
Why do you two enjoy torturing me?
- Because it's fun.
- Yeah, Dad, 'cause it's fun!
- Oh, here we go.
- [Ted groans]
[Ted] Oh, boy.
Hoo!
But enough of me blabbering.
Who here wants to see some fireworks?
[cheering]
Come on, now, you can do better than that.
Who here wants to see some fireworks?
[loud cheering]
["Semper Fidelis" playing]
[Karen sighs]
Uh, why are we stopping?
Because I slipped Jimmy a five.
You what?
Come on,
these are the best seats in the house.
The best seats in the house.
- [fireworks popping]
- Oh!
Happy Fourth of July!
[cheering]
[Karen] Whoa!
[laughing]
- That was pretty, wasn't it?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
[Karen gasps]
[ominous synth music playing]
[rustling in trees]
Mom, the trees.
- What, baby?
- The trees are moving.
[rustling continues]
Why are you looking at the trees, baby?
The fireworks. Look at the fireworks!
[Karen laughs] That was a big one,
wasn't it?
[thudding footsteps]
[creature snarling]
[theme song playing]
[fireworks popping
and crackling distantly]
[crowd cheering distantly]
[marching band playing distantly]
[Eleven] He said he was
building something.
That it was all for me.
Building something...
- Is he talking about the flayed?
- He must be.
So, he's building an army,
just like we thought.
Yeah, but he's not building this army
to spread.
He's building it to stop Eleven.
Last year, El closed the gate on him.
I have a feeling
that really pissed him off.
Like, royally.
And the Mind Flayer now knows that
she's the only thing that can stop him.
- But if she's out of the way...
- Game over.
He also said
he was gonna kill all of you.
Yeah, well, that's nice.
[faint screeching noise]
[ominous synth music playing]
Do you guys hear that?
[Nancy shudders]
It's just the fireworks.
Billy...
When he told you this,
it was here, in this room?
[distant thudding noise]
[fluttering sound]
He knows we're here.
[trees rustling]
[creature snarls]
[creature screeches]
[alarm blaring]
[slurring] Jesus, slow down!
[slurring] Yeah, what is this,
like, the Indy 500?
It's the Indy 300.
- No, dingus, it's 500!
- It's 300!
Let's say a million.
[both laughing loudly]
- What is wrong with them?
- I don't know.
- [Erica] Dustin, watch out!
- [Dustin] Shit!
[Steve grunts, yells]
- Oh!
- [Robin groans]
You guys all right back there?
[both groaning]
They're fine.
Come on. We gotta go, now.
- Come on! Get out!
- Let's go!
[Steve] Ow!
- [Steve] We're coming!
- Here goes nothin'.
- [Steve] This sucks.
- [beeping]
[Robin and Steve whooping giddily]
- Hey! You look like you're surfing!
- Surfing! Yeah!
[Steve] Whoa!
- They seem drunk.
- Why would they be drunk?
I'm a natural! Check it out!
Whoop!
[Robin laughs]
Wipeout!
[both laughing]
- He's burning up.
- [Steve] You're burning up.
- One sec, one sec. Steve, Steve.
- [Steve] God, no.
Ow!
His pupils are super dilated.
Maybe he's drugged.
Ugh. Boop!
Steve, are you drugged?
How many times, Dad?
I don't do drugs. It's only marijuana.
This isn't funny, okay?
I need to know what they did to you.
- Are you gonna die on us?
- Boop.
We all die,
my strange little child friend.
It's just a matter of how...
and when.
They're gonna be looking for us up there,
so I need you to tell me
where you parked your car.
Oh, can we make a pit stop
at the food court?
- I would kill for a hot dog on a stick.
- Ooh!
All right. Yeah, food.
Yes, you can have
as much food as you want,
but only if you tell me
where your car is parked.
- Uh-oh.
- Uh-oh?
The car's off the board.
- What?
- They took the keys.
The Russians, they took the keys.
Like, forever ago.
[Robin and Steve laugh]
That's a bummer, right?
[Robin laughing]
[Robin and Steve] Oh!
Oh, my God, that tastes so good. Ah!
Steve, can you taste the air?
I taste it! I taste it!
- Stop!
- Shit! Come on! Come on!
- [kids clamoring]
- [in Russian] Stop right there!
- [Robin] Okay, okay, okay! Woo!
- Why are we running?
[Robin laughing]
[Eleven grunting]
[Mike] Yeah. That's good like that.
Hey, get away from the windows.
[all panting]
[lamp squeaking]
[rumbling]
[electric crackling]
[gasping]
[breathing rapidly]
It's close.
[leaves rustling]
[branches snapping]
[rumbling footsteps]
[glasses clinking]
[rumbling stops]
Where'd it go?
[Nancy exhales sharply]
[shuddering breaths]
- [creature shrieks]
- [all gasping]
[yells, grunts]
- [creature shrieks]
- [Jonathan grunts]
[Jonathan yells]
[grunts]
- [shrieks]
- [Jonathan groans]
[shrieks]
[creature wails, screeches]
[creature wails]
[shrieking in pain]
[gasps]
[creature shrieking]
[creature screams]
[Eleven yells]
[creature shrieks]
[Max yelps]
Holy shit.
[shrieking]
- [glass shatters]
- [shrieking]
[panting]
[creatures shrieking]
[shrieking and barking]
[yells]
- [whimpering shrieks]
- [panting]
[roaring and shrieking]
[Eleven screams]
El!
[screaming]
[Mike] El!
- [all grunting]
- [creature roaring]
[pumps shotgun]
[roaring]
[Mike] Pull!
[Jonathan] Nancy, shoot it!
[screaming]
[snarling]
[pained snarls]
[Eleven screams]
[Max] Come on! Lucas!
[Nancy pumps shotgun]
[yells]
[roars]
[Lucas grunts, yells]
[shotgun fires]
[roaring]
[screaming]
- [kids straining]
- [creature roars]
[yells]
[Max] Pull!
- [shotgun fires]
- [creature screeches]
- [squelching]
- [roaring]
El! El, you okay?
[creature roaring]
[shrieking]
[screeching in pain]
[monstrous chittering]
[creature snarls]
[panting heavily]
[roaring]
[Eleven panting]
[creature shrieking]
[roaring]
[yelling]
[pained screeching]
[yells]
[distant roaring]
- [Nancy] Go, go, go!
- [Jonathan] Come on, come on, go!
- [Nancy] Go!
- [Jonathan] Hurry up! Come on!
[Mike] Everybody out!
- [Jonathan] Go!
- [Nancy] Go, come on!
- [creature roars]
- [Jonathan] Go, go, go, go!
- [Lucas] Come on!
- [Nancy repeating] Come on!
[Lucas] Come on! Come on!
[creature shrieking]
[Jonathan] Get in. Right here.
[Eleven wails in pain]
- Drive! Drive!
- [engine starting]
[roaring]
- [Steve] Whoa!
- Where are we going?
- Just trust me.
- [Robin laughs]
All clear.
[score from Back to the Future playing]
[Marty] Doc!
What did I tell you?!
Eighty-eight miles per hour!
[Dustin] Come on.
- [metal clanging in movie]
- [Doc gasps]
[Doc] The temporal displacement occurred
exactly 1:20...
- You two, sit.
- No, no, no! These seats are too close!
- Dude, these seats blow.
- Then don't watch the movie.
- We wanna watch it.
- Then watch it!
- Shh!
Sorry.
Whatever you do,
don't... go... anywhere.
- Fine, Dad.
- [Robin snickers]
[Doc] The appropriate question is
"When the hell are they?"
You see, Einstein has just become
- the world's first time traveler!
- Sorry. Sorry.
- [Doc] I sent him... into the future!
- [Dustin sighs]
Okay, it's official.
I'm never having kids.
- What are we doing here?
- We're laying low.
Cooling off.
Like Oswald.
Oswald was found in a theater
and shot to death.
A week later.
The point is, his plan didn't work.
Only because it was a setup.
- What?
- He was just a patsy.
- Tell me you're joking.
- Shh!
[Erica and Dustin] Shh!
We need to get outta here.
All right, you watch
Tweedledee and Tweedledum.
- Make sure they don't go anywhere.
- Where are you going?
To find us a ride.
[Doc] Look out!
[DeLorean zapping]
[brakes screeching]
[Marty] Doc...
- What's happening?
- I have no idea.
[Marty] Are you telling me that
you built a time machine...
[Alexei speaking Russian]
- What's he saying?
- He's showing me the location of the key
to turn off the machine.
[speaking Russian]
- Sorry, "keys." Two keys.
- [Alexei speaking Russian]
Two-man rule.
- Two-man rule?
- Yeah, two men, two keys, like a...
nuclear launch.
But, uh, to retrieve the keys,
there is a vault.
- [speaking Russian]
- And to open the vault,
you need to enter Planck's constant.
- Planck's what?
- Planck's constant.
- It's a very famous number.
- All right, so we get the keys,
and then we turn the machine off.
That's what he says.
All right, well, that shouldn't be
too hard. We can do this.
Joyce, did you hear the part
where he said the place was like
an impenetrable fortress?
Yeah, but there has to be a way in.
Yeah, there is. Our military.
- Who are coming.
- Well, we don't know that anymore
because you yelled at them
like it was a parent-teacher conference,
and then you hung up on them,
so we don't know what the hell's going on,
because now we're...
Wait, wait, what are we do... Oh!
Wait, that's right!
We're on our way to rescue our children
from the big, bad
Fourth of July celebration!
You know what, if you can't handle this,
then just turn around
and drop me off first.
What are you gonna do?
You gonna walk back to Hawkins?
I will do anything
if it gets me away from you!
Children! Children! Children!
This interminable bickering
was amusing at first,
but it's getting very stale and we've
still got a long drive ahead of us.
So, why don't you two cut the horseshit
and get to the part where you admit
your sexual feelings for one another?
- Whoa!
- You are way off base, buddy!
Oh, spare me, spare me, spare me!
Yes, yes, he's a brute. I know.
Probably reminds you
of a bad relationship,
and, gosh, you'd really like a nice man
to settle down with,
but, admit it, you're real curious to know
what he's like in the sack.
And you. Ha!
Well, you're just a big manbaby
who'd rather act tough
than show his true feelings,
because the last time
you opened your heart, you got hurt.
Owie.
And now, rather than admit these feelings,
you're dancing around one another
with this mind-numbing
and frankly boorish mating ritual.
So, please, for my sake,
either quit your bickering, or pull over,
tear off those clothes,
and get it over with already!
[gasps]
[deep sigh]
[in Russian] What was that?
[in Russian]
I told them they should have sex.
They have not had sex?
No.
[snickers]
[chuckles]
[both laughing]
[Joyce mutters]
[Alexei speaking Russian]
[both laughing]
[Murray laughs] Oh! Oh!
[Murray and Alexei continue laughing]
[tires squealing]
[glass shattering]
[Eleven groans]
Okay, get her down.
[Nancy] Okay.
Lemme see.
- Oh, shit.
- [groans]
What... What... Hey, what are you doing?
I'm cleaning the wound.
No, first, we need to stop the bleeding,
then clean, then disinfect, then bandage.
I skateboard. Trust me.
Mike, hold this.
[groans]
Keep the pressure on it,
nice and firm, okay?
We're gonna need water, soap.
- Yeah, okay.
- All right.
Does any of this help?
No.
Go get me a washcloth and a bowl.
- A bowl?
- Lucas.
- Go.
- [stammers] Okay.
[groans]
[Nancy] What did that thing
look like to you?
Like that thing in the hospital,
only bigger.
Yeah, a lot bigger.
Like, Tom and Bruce,
they merged to become one, right?
And... And Driscoll kept saying
how she needed to go back to the source...
Wait, you think Driscoll's in there?
Maybe.
And... And... And maybe Heather and Janet,
too, and God knows who else.
I don't know how we're gonna
kill this thing, but if we do...
- We kill all the flayed.
- And... we end this.
Maybe.
All I know is...
we need El.
[Lucas] Bowl...
Bowl...
- Why wouldn't it be with the cereal?
- I don't know.
What else do you use a bowl for?
I... I don't know.
[Lucas sighs]
Oh, shit.
Satan's Baby.
You ever shot one of these suckers?
No. Is it sweet?
- That's an understatement.
- [Max] That doesn't look like a bowl.
Nah, it's way better.
There is a reason this warning label
says "18 or older."
This sucker is filled with 150 grains
of black powder.
AKA gunpowder.
Strap two of these together,
and it's bigger than an M-80.
Five of them,
we've got ourselves a stick of dynamite.
You wanna kill that thing with fireworks?
Do you have a better idea?
Uh, yeah. Eleven.
Against that thing?
She's gonna need some backup.
- Oh, my God.
- [Lucas scoffs]
Hold this.
[Mike groans]
Does that hurt?
Uh, not bad.
You're gonna have an awesome scar.
You'll look even more badass.
Bitchin'.
Yeah, bitchin'.
[chuckles]
El...
Yeah?
I've been meaning to tell you something.
It's just, being broken up,
it's been hard.
[distorted radio chatter]
And...
I like that you and Max are friends now.
It's just, I was jealous at first,
and... and angry.
And that's why I said
all that stupid stuff.
And it's like I wanted you all to myself.
And now I realize how unfair that is.
And selfish. And, like... I'm sorry.
I just, like, I've never felt like this,
you know, with anyone before...
and...
[sighs] You know, they do say
it makes you crazy.
What makes you crazy?
You never... You never heard that term...
You know, like the phrase, like...
"blank makes you crazy," like the word...
- "Girlfriends"?
- No, no, no, no, not... not girlfriends.
- "Boyfriends."
- No! No, no, not boyfriends either.
- It's like... It's like a feeling or...
- [softly] A feeling...
Yeah, like something... Like, old people
say it to each other sometimes.
- Old people?
- Yeah.
What I wanna say is...
that I just...
I know that I...
- [Dustin speaking via radio, garbled]
- [static popping]
[Dustin, distorted via radio]
I repeat... this is a code red!
- [score from Back to the Future plays]
- Dustin?
Mike?
- [Mike] Dustin!
- Mike!
Oh, my God, you have to listen.
I know I've been MIA,
and I'm sorry, it's not because I'm mad.
I mean, I actually was mad,
but it's also because
I was trapped underground
in a secret Russian base.
[garbled radio audio]
Dustin, you're going way too fast.
I can't understand you.
I know that sounds insane,
but the Russians have infiltrated Hawkins!
The goddamn Russians!
And now... they're using...
to open the gate.
Dustin, you're... you're breaking up.
And now they're after us
and we don't have a way out of here,
so I need you to come and get us.
Can Nancy drive?
[garbled radio audio]
Dustin, you're cutting out.
- Mike?
- Dustin, you there?
Mike? Mike, do you copy?
Dustin...
[powering down noise]
Shit! Not now. Please, not now. Mike!
- Dustin!
- Mike!
[static hissing]
What is it?
Do you have any batteries? Double-A?
Why would I have batteries?
I always carry batteries.
Then what's the problem?
I need eight.
Eight?
Shit. Guess we'll have to go to plan B.
Plan B? What's plan B?
[film score crescendos]
Where... are they?
That's amazing.
So, like, I wasn't totally focused
in there or anything, but...
I'm pretty sure...
that mom was trying to bang her son.
Wait, wait, the hot chick
was Alex P. Keaton's mom?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
But they're the same age.
No, but he went back in time.
[snickers]
Then why is it called Back to the Future?
He has to go back to the future
because he's in the past.
So, the future is actually the present,
which is his time.
Wh... What?
No, no, it's my turn. You've had enough.
[Robin grunts contentedly]
[gentle synth music playing]
[echoing] Wow.
[twinkling]
[echoing] Hey, Robin.
You gotta check this out.
- [grunts]
- Check this...
This... The ceiling, it's beautiful.
[echoing] Oh, wow.
[chuckles]
Oh.
[Robin chuckles]
[grunts]
[Steve groans]
[synth music distorts]
[twinkling]
[Steve grunts]
[Robin coughs]
[Robin retches and spits]
[cheering]
[carnival music playing]
[Hopper yells]
Stay here,
go over the plans with Smirnoff.
- I can help look.
- No, you'll scare the children.
- Jim, if this is about earlier...
- Stay put, Freud!
You hear me? Stay put!
[Murray sighs]
[kids screaming and laughing]
You know,
say what you will about Kline,
he certainly knows how to throw a party.
I'm sorry about him, by the way.
- Who, Larry?
- No, Murray.
He's a sick individual
who likes to get under people's skin.
So, let's not let him, you know,
get under our skin.
I'm not, I haven't.
I just, you seem
a little more quiet than usual.
- I just... I just wanna find the kids.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[Larry] I'll give it my best shot.
- [bell clanging]
- [Larry exclaims]
[man] You won yourself a bear!
Thank you. Here you go. [chuckles]
[photographer] Mayor Kline!
[photographer] One more, one more.
[photographer] Big smile. There we go.
[cheering]
- Watch it!
- [man 2] Happy Fourth, dick.
- [panting]
- [dialing on car phone]
[line ringing]
Come on, come on, come on!
Pick up, pick up, pick up,
you commie bastards!
[ominous synth music playing]
[freezer humming]
[pull-tab clicks loudly]
- [whispers] Quiet.
- [whispers] Oh, sorry.
- How do you even drink that?
- Because it's delicious.
[Mike and Max] What?
It's like Carpenter's The Thing.
The original is a classic,
no question about it.
But the remake...
[slurping loudly]
[satisfied sigh]
[smacking lips]
Sweeter, bolder...
better.
You're insane.
So, you prefer the original Thing?
What? No, I'm not talking about The Thing,
I'm talking about New Coke.
It's the same concept, dude.
Uh, actually, it's not the same concept.
It is the same concept.
- No, it's not.
- [yells] Yes, it is.
Hey.
Sorry.
Did you... find him?
[Lucas] The movies?
Dustin's so freaked out about the gate,
he decides to go watch a movie?
Yeah, makes total sense.
You're positive he said "gate"
and not "great"?
Yeah, like,
"This movie I'm watching is great."
Sounded like "gate."
Which would explain how
the Mind Flayer's still alive.
- Yeah, we just have to shut it again.
- Then the monster dies.
But if not,
we always have Lucas' fireworks.
Keep mocking my plan, Max.
Keep mocking it.
I wanna hear you say it again,
because you keep doubting me.
You keep doubting me!
- [Max] Ridiculous.
- [Lucas] Will?
We're gonna prove 'em wrong, right?
[eerie synth music playing]
[screeching]
[Steve groans]
The ceiling stopped spinning for me.
Is it still spinning for you?
Holy shit.
No.
You think we puked it all up?
Maybe. Ask me something.
[in Russian accent] Interrogate me.
Okay. Interrogate you. Sure.
Um...
When was the last time
you, uh, peed your pants?
Today.
What?
When the Russian doctor
took out the bone saw.
[laughs] Oh, my God.
It was just a little bit, though.
Yeah, it's definitely still in her system.
[laughs]
[groans]
[Robin] Oh...
- All right, my turn.
- Okay.
Hit me.
Have you...
ever been in love?
Yep. Nancy Wheeler.
First semester, senior year.
[imitates gunshot, chuckles]
Oh, my God.
She's such a priss.
[Steve] Hm.
Turns out, not really.
[scoffs]
Are you still in love with Nancy?
- No.
- Why not?
I think it's because I found someone
who's a little bit better for me.
[chuckles] It's crazy.
Ever since Dustin got home,
he's been saying,
"You know, you gotta find your Suzie.
You gotta find your Suzie."
Wait, who's Suzie?
It's some girl from camp,
I guess his girlfriend.
To be honest with you,
I'm not 100% sure she's even real.
But that's not...
that's not really the point.
That doesn't matter. The point is,
this girl, you know, the one that I like,
it's somebody that I...
didn't even talk to in school.
And I don't even know why.
Maybe 'cause Tommy H.
would've made fun of me or...
I wouldn't be...
prom king.
It's stupid. I mean, Dustin's right,
it's all just a bunch of bullshit anyways.
Because, when I think about it,
I should've been hanging out
with this girl the whole time.
First of all, she's hilarious.
She's so funny.
I feel like, this summer,
I have laughed harder
than I have laughed...
in a really long time.
And she's smart.
Way smarter than me.
You know, she can crack, like,
top secret Russian codes and...
You know? She's honestly unlike anyone
I've ever even met before.
Robin?
[tapping on stall]
Robin, did you just OD in there?
No. [sighs]
I...
am still alive.
[deep sigh]
[Robin] The floor's disgusting.
Yeah, well, I already got a bunch of blood
and puke on my shirt, so...
What do you think?
About?
This girl.
She sounds awesome.
She is awesome. And what about the guy?
I think he's on drugs,
and he's not thinking straight.
Really? 'Cause I think he's thinking
a lot more clearly than usual.
He's not.
Look...
he doesn't even know this girl.
And if he did know her,
like... like really know her,
I don't think he'd even want to be
her friend.
No, that's not true. No way is that true.
Listen to me, Steve.
It's shocked me to my core,
but I like you.
I really like you.
But I'm not like your other friends.
And I'm not like Nancy Wheeler.
Robin, that's exactly why I like you.
[Robin scoffs]
Do you remember what I said
about Click's class?
About me being jealous and, like,
obsessed?
Yeah.
It isn't because I had a crush on you.
It's because...
she wouldn't stop staring at you.
Mrs. Click?
[chuckles]
Tammy Thompson.
I wanted her to look at me.
But... she couldn't
pull her eyes away from you
and your stupid hair.
And I didn't understand,
because you would get
bagel crumbs all over the floor.
And you asked dumb questions.
And you were a douchebag.
And... And you didn't even like her and...
I would go home...
and just scream into my pillow.
But Tammy Thompson's a girl.
[softly] Steve.
Yeah?
Oh.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
Steve...
did you OD over there?
No, I just, uh...
just thinking.
Okay.
I mean, yeah.
Tammy Thompson, you know,
she's cute and all, but...
I mean,
she's a total dud.
She is not.
Yes, she is.
She wants to be, like, a singer.
She wants to move to, like,
Nashville and shit.
- She has dreams.
- She can't even hold a tune.
She's practically tone-deaf.
Have you heard her?
- [Robin chuckles]
- All the time.
[singing atonally]
♪ You see me now tonight ♪
- Shut up.
- ♪ You see me... ♪
- She does not sound like that.
- She sounds exactly...
- That's a great impersonation of her.
- She does not.
You sound like a Muppet.
She sounds like a Muppet.
She sounds like a Muppet giving birth.
[both laughing]
[sings like Kermit]
♪ And if you could hold me tight ♪
[both sing atonally]
♪ We'll be holding on forever ♪
- Exactly.
- [laughs] I know!
Okay.
What the hell?
[both laugh]
[intense synth music playing]
[creature shrieks weakly]
[monstrous screeching]
[cheering and laughing]
[Alexei, in Russian] And why all this?
If I just turn the keys,
it's like turning off a car.
But then the car still works, does it not?
[in Russian] Yes.
And do you want the car to still work
or do you want it to explode?
I want the car to explode.
Good. Then do this.
Just make sure you are nowhere near it
when it does. It is not pretty.
Turns people into dust.
And then...
It's over.
[chuckles]
And I become an American citizen
and join in the fun, yes?
Who said you had to be an American
to join the fun?
[carnival music playing]
[crowd cheering]
[in Russian] It doesn't get
more American than this, my friend.
Fatty foods, ugly decadence,
rigged games...
[in English] Fifteen tickets, please.
[cheering]
- They are rigged, these games?
- [in Russian] Yes.
[balloon pops]
They do not look rigged.
That's just it, my dear Alexei.
They have been designed
to present the illusion of fairness!
But it's all a scam, a trick,
to put your money
in the rich man's pocket.
That, my dear friend, is...
America.
But, hey...
knock yourself out.
[carnival barker yelling]
Where are you going?
To get us the closest thing to food
I can find.
Hey. Hey.
[Joyce] Karen.
[carnival barker] Step right up!
[Karen]...feel the wind push you back
and it's gonna...
- [Ted] Hold on. Do we have seat belts?
- Hey, Karen.
Joyce!
Oh, my gosh! How funny to see you here!
Where are the kids?
I... I haven't seen them.
I don't think they're here yet.
- You three, up against the wall!
- No, where are they?
Oh, my gosh,
I can hardly keep track these days.
Uh, they were at, uh...
Dustin's, then Lucas's,
- then Max's.
- Max...
- You know how it is. Summer!
- [alarm blaring]
Probably getting into some kinda trouble.
[ride door whirring]
Last warning, you two.
Up against the wall!
Hold the ride!
On your life, Magnum.
[all exclaiming]
[Ted murmurs]
Woo! Here we go!
Holy smokes!
[Ted] Holy smokes!
[rapid carnival music playing]
[Doc] Roads?
Where we're going,
we don't need roads.
[cheering]
[indistinct chatter]
[door hinge creaking]
[Dustin] And...
blend.
[woman] It is so good!
- Well, shit, that worked.
- Course it worked.
We just have to get on the bus
with the rest of these plebes,
and home sweet home, here we come.
- Uh, Dustin?
- What?
Yeah, we might not wanna
go to your house.
Why?
Well, I might've told them your full name.
- What is wrong with you?
- Dude, I was drugged.
- So?
So, you resist. You tough it out.
You tough it out like a man.
Oh, yeah, it's easy for you to say.
Guys?
Sorry for the inconvenience.
Have a pleasant evening.
Abort.
[suspenseful music playing]
Abort. Abort.
[panting]
[Steve] Shit.
[Robin] Okay.
[Steve] Come on, let's go, let's go.
[onlookers cheering]
That's three green!
And here's dart number four!
[carnival music playing]
[cheering]
One more for the big prize!
You can do it, mister!
- [bell ringing]
- [loud cheering]
[man] We have a winner!
[barker] Step right up,
ladies and gentlemen!
Get your tickets right here!
Murray!
[in Russian] Look!
It's not rigged!
Ah!
[laughs like Woody Woodpecker]
It's not rigged.
[Murray laughs heartily]
[ominous music playing]
[carnival audio fades]
[silenced gunshot]
[in Russian] Traitor.
[faintly] Alexei!
[feedback whining]
[clown's laughter echoing in slow motion]
[resuming normal volume] Alexei!
[carnival audio resumes]
[in English] Oh, no. Oh, my God. Let's go.
[Alexei grunts and coughs]
- Easy.
- [Alexei groans]
[in Russian] Keep pressure on it.
I'll get you help.
I'll get help.
[suspenseful synth music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[crowd cheering]
Jim... Jim.
Jim!
They got Alexei, Jim!
Jim! Alexei! They got Alexei, Jim!
[exhales sharply]
We gotta go.
- We gotta go.
- What?
[Hopper] Let's go.
They make an odd couple, don't they?
Well, it's like they say,
there's someone for everyone.
[carnival music playing]
[bell ringing]
[Karen sighs deeply]
[suspenseful music playing]
[crowd exclaims]
[male vendor] Who wants a hot dog?
Find Murray, get the car,
- bring it around back.
- Okay.
[recording of cackling laughter]
[in Russian] Heading to "Big Top."
Northeast side of the fair.
[carnival barker] Step right up,
ladies and gentlemen!
Get your tickets to the Big Top here!
[barker speaking indistinctly]
...this side of the Mississippi.
Hey! Get your kids outta here! Police!
Get 'em out of here! Go!
[barker] You, sir!
Step on up!
I see you eyeing the maze!
Don't be surprised! Don't be scared!
[crowd cheering]
[barker] Step on up, sir!
[recording of cackling laughter]
[eerie male voice]
Do you dare enter the cave of horrors?
You never know what you might find
around the corner.
[recording of eerie giggling]
Don't show your fear
in the presence of the tiger.
[tiger's roar sounds]
Or you may never escape this cave alive.
- [tiger's roar sounds]
- [Hopper yells]
[fighting grunts]
[gasps]
[screams]
[panting]
Alexei!
Oh, my God.
I... I just left for a minute...
for a corn dog.
- [Joyce cries]
- A stupid corn dog.
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
- [man grunts]
- [carnival music playing]
[fighting grunts]
[man groans]
[Hopper yells]
[Hopper grunts]
[man wails in pain]
[man groans]
[Hopper yells]
[intense synth music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[panting]
[indistinct male voice on radio]
[man on radio, in Russian]
Vasilev, are you there? Vasilev? Answer!
[male voice continues in Russian]
[tiger's roar sounds]
[recording of cackling laughter]
[carnival music playing]
What are you doing?
Hey!
- Larry.
- Joyce.
[Joyce grunts]
[Larry wails in pain]
Ooh! [groans]
[man] Yeah, lady!
[suspenseful synth music playing]
[silenced gunshots]
[Hopper] Hey.
[men speaking Russian]
[gasps]
[recording of cackling laughter]
[gasps for air, groans]
[Grigori coughs]
[man, in Russian] Comrade!
Get off me!
[recording of cackling laughter]
[sighs]
Goddamn!
Son of a bitch!
[grunting]
[groans]
[grunts]
Hey!
[Hopper] Hit it. Hit it! Go! Go!
Alexei?
[man on radio, in Russian]
On the lower level...
Hey, translate.
We've found the children.
They are still in the mall. Lower level.
[in Russian]
Keep all entrances locked down.
I repeat...
[squeaking sound]
[quietly] Everyone, get over here.
I found them.
[kids panting]
[panting]
- [car alarm wailing]
- [all gasping]
[horn honking]
[in Russian] What the hell?
[intense synth music playing]
[men groaning]
[steam hissing]
[metal clattering]
[dramatic synth music playing]
[laughing] You flung that thing
like a Hot Wheel!
[Dustin grunts]
- Lucas?
- What are you doing here?
Ask them. It's their fault.
True, yeah. Totally true.
It's absolutely our fault.
I don't understand what happened
to that car.
El has superpowers.
- [Robin] I'm sorry?
- Superpowers. She threw it with her mind.
- C'mon, catch up.
- That's El?
- Who's El?
- I'm sorry, who are you?
- I'm Robin. I work with Steve.
- She cracked the top secret code.
Yeah, which is how we found out
about the Russians.
Russians? Wait, what Russians?
- The Russians!
- Those were Russians?
- Some of them.
- What are you talking about?
- Didn't you hear our code red?
- Yeah.
- Couldn't understand what you were saying.
- Goddamn low battery.
How many times do I have to tell you
with the low battery?
Well, everything worked out, didn't it?
- Worked out? We almost died.
- Yeah, but we didn't, did we?
- [Steve] It was pretty damn close.
- [Lucas] Okay, Russians?
As in, they're working for
the Russian government?
- [Eleven panting]
- [Dustin] What are you not comprehending?
Am I not speaking English?
- We have a full-blown Red Dawn situation.
- [droning sound]
[Max] So this has nothing to do
with the gate?
[Dustin] It has everything to do
with the gate...
[droning sound intensifies]
[Eleven grunts, groans]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- El! El!
- [whimpering]
- [Erica] What's wrong with her?
- What's wrong?
My leg. My leg.
Her leg, her leg. Okay.
[Eleven panting]
- Get that off.
- Okay.
[all exclaim in disgust]
[Erica groans]
[gasps]
[intense synth music playing]
[grunting]
[wailing]
El! El!
[Mike] El! El, are you okay?
El!
[screaming]
[intense synth music playing]
[monkey screeching]